# **Mars Huang**

Front-End Developer

React | Vue | TypeScript | JavaScript | Salesforce LWC | RWD
Tailwind CSS | Dynamics 365 | Material UI | Git | SEO | SPA
NodeJS | Styled Components | CSS | HTML | Google Cloud | C

#### **SUMMARY**

Front-end developer with over 3 years of experience. Proficient in JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Tailwind CSS, and Vue. RESTful and Node.js backend integration. Prioritize user experience (UX) and developer experience (DX), maintainable solutions such as architecture, and documentation. Native Mandarin speaker, fluent in English and French. SEO and PageSpeed Insights performance improvements, scores from 83 to 100.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Trend Micro**, Taipei — Front-End Developer

May 2023 - Present July 2020 - April 2022

### Online Help Center 🗹

- Built using React, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Dynamics 365.
- UI handles 400K articles and serves 10M users across 29 languages (i18n).
- Solr Search, Azure, Microsoft Power Automate integration.
- Improved developer experience, built documentation for better version control, reduced communication time by 50%.

## BSP 2.0 (Business Success Portal)

- Built with Salesforce LWC (Lightning Web Component), make scalable components, reduced future maintenance time by 80%.
- Website with 4.5M users and 19M page views per year.
- Worked with remote developers, refined user-experience.

#### Tomo-Chatbot ☑

- SPA for AI bot, built with VueJS, handled RESTful APIs.

## **Arcadyan**, Hsinchu — Software Engineer

October 2019 - July 2020

- UI service on firmware, maintained HTTP server, Git version control.

No. 30, Beixin St, Taoyuan District

(+886) 932-523-366 mars.hs.huang@gmail.com https://flying-musk.github.io

#### **Education**

# National Chiao Tung University,

Electrical and Computer Engineering (GPA 3.31)

Sept. 2015 - June 2019

#### **LANGUAGES**

French:
DELF B2
TCF Canada B2

English: IELTS 7.5 TOEIC L/R 955, TOEIC S/W 180/180